cdischina.com 2011-09-01

# Chengdu International School - Privacy Policy

Our Web servers automatically log the IP address of your computer, the browser type and browser version you are using. We also track what pages you visit on our site. Forms you submit to us may also automatically log this information as well as the date and time the form was submitted. We use this information for statistical purposes and under no circumstances can the information we collect identify you personally. You remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided this Web site with personal information.

This Web site collects personal information only when voluntarily submitted by the site visitor. This information is used only for one purpose: To follow up on a request for additional communication.

We will not sell or share this information with others except to comply with legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others.

We may also disclose information collected to trusted contractors, vendors, agents or affiliates, doing business or conducting activities on our behalf.

By visiting this site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. ISC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and without notification other than by updating this page.

If you have questions about this policy, you can email us at: [c.wells@LDIUS.org](mailto:c.wells@LDIUS.org)
